[Music]
it is far too early for winter but i did
see a sprinkling of snow up in the
mountains today and realize no doubt
it'll reach me before the autumn is over
i would love a few more months to enjoy
the golden fields covered in leaves but
i still need to prepare for the ice and
snow
i got to visit my sister last week and
so i only had time to film little
snippets from my days at the cottage but
i thought i'd still share a little of
what i've been up to
[Music]
so
while my flowers are all but gone due to
more frost i did manage to save some
containers by bringing them indoors i
will no doubt keep these around long
after they have wilted and left pollen
everywhere because i always forget until
they're completely dead
i recently received a letter from a
lovely viewer who said they just started
a creative career and were wondering
what inspired me to pursue mine
especially in regards to my art business
and creating videos
this is something i've been reflecting
on recently because now that i've been
doing it for a while i've been able to
learn a lot and make many mistakes along
the way
i mentioned this in a past video but i
thought i'd reiterate that i believe the
most important thing you can do whenever
you start out on a new life or career
path is to know what you believe in
regards to your own values and the
vision behind what you're doing
for example i always wanted to be able
to create the art i love and share it
with people
whether or not that meant i could rely
on it for a living which thankfully is
now my main job
if you have watched my art related
videos and seen my work you know that my
art style is
a niche to say the least it takes a lot
of inspiration from fairy tales and
children's illustration
it doesn't appeal to a mass audience and
i never intended it to
because i knew that if i completely
changed my art style or what i created
just to be more successful that my
passion for it would disappear
i would rather do any other type of job
then deny what i love to create
that is also why i don't do sponsorships
as you may have noticed because before i
started my channel i decided it didn't
align with what i was personally trying
to communicate
and that of course is not a reflection
on other creators who do
because i completely support them and am
so happy it lets them keep creating
it just didn't fit into the philosophy
of my personal channel and consequently
i felt more free to occasionally
highlight small businesses just starting
out that can't afford to do sponsorships
i want to pay these artists since i was
in their position not too long ago and
it feels like a meaningful way to give
back
[Music]
i think that when we achieve a goal or
the success we had in our mind's eye
you're often left with the question of
what now
because there will always be someone out
there that seems to be more successful
or better at something than you
it is so easy to compare with someone
ahead of you and find yourself short
instead of looking back and being amazed
at so proud of how far you've come
[Music]
that's something that means a lot to me
and as my channel has grown i've held on
so tightly to the philosophy i had when
i first started
of course we should always be flexible
and open to expand our beliefs as long
as we don't lose sight of what's truly
important to us and what we set out to
do in the first place
for example there are so many things i
could change about my videos and content
that would no doubt attract a broader
audience than i have now
but then i would be wandering off the
path of what i initially wanted to do
in my case it was to afford living while
also connecting with kindred spirits
inspiring others to go outdoors and
preserve wild lands
enjoy the magic of simply living day to
day
everything else is simply a bonus
[Music]
so
in short follow your heart always
because when your inner self and outer
actions are in alignment i believe that
is when you can meet your full potential
and find lasting joy in the process
i hope you have a lovely day or night
and i'm sending you my love